<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Fill the memory</title>
    <link>https://fillmem.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Fill the memory</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 17:41:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://fillmem.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Vanilla JavaScript: Create a HTML Element</title>
      <link>https://fillmem.com/post/create-html-element-with-vanilla-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 17:41:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fillmem.com/post/create-html-element-with-vanilla-javascript/</guid>
      <description>In all the frontend projects I had been involved with, we ended up to need to add HTML elements dynamically to a web page.
Functions to create HTML elements There are many implementations around the web of this small feature, but I find this one below to be the clearer and easiest version to use. This version has also the advantage to be vanilla js.
/** * creates a HTML element ready to be append.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IntelliJ IDEA and IdeaVim key does not repeat</title>
      <link>https://fillmem.com/post/intellij-ideavim-repeat-key/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 17:30:50 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fillmem.com/post/intellij-ideavim-repeat-key/</guid>
      <description>When I started C language years ago, I became a Vim editor developer. Since then, for all my backend developments, I have been faithful to Vim.
Few weeks ago, when I started to code in Elixir, I started as well to use IntelliJ IDEA with the Elixir plugin and obviously the Vim plugin.
On OSX, when you use the combination IntelliJ and IdeaVim it can happen that the keys you hold does not repeat themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fix &#34;library not loaded&#34; error with Brew</title>
      <link>https://fillmem.com/post/library-not-loaded-osx-brew/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 23:47:27 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fillmem.com/post/library-not-loaded-osx-brew/</guid>
      <description>Ruby, PHP and a lot other languages rely on system libraries to provide some features in their own ecosystems. It times to times leads to this kind of error
Library not loaded: /usr/local/lib/libjpeg.8.dylib  A large majority of developers on OSX use Brew package manager to install the libraries they need. On the above library loading error, the immediate reaction is so to brew install it
brew install libjpeg Warning: jpeg 9c is already installed and up-to-date To reinstall 9c, run `brew reinstall jpeg`  In most of the cases, you don&amp;rsquo;t have the library missing installed and you can continue with you main task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker&#39;s first aid for software developers</title>
      <link>https://fillmem.com/post/docker-tips-software-developers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 05:45:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fillmem.com/post/docker-tips-software-developers/</guid>
      <description>Note: If you have as well some tricks to cover you when you use Docker, I&amp;rsquo;ll be pleased to add them
As a software developer, I work with Docker quite rarely. I create at the beginning of a project:
 the scripts to build the needed custom docker images the scripts to launch quickly the docker containers and that&amp;rsquo;s almost all.  If you&amp;rsquo;re like me, you probably forget quickly the Docker way or the tips and after 30 mins of déjà vu digging, you get frustrated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build a fast, secured and free static site in less than 3 hours</title>
      <link>https://fillmem.com/post/fast-secured-and-free-static-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 06:09:06 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fillmem.com/post/fast-secured-and-free-static-site/</guid>
      <description>Note: Unless you&amp;rsquo;re a developer or you want to learn how to do sites, my first advice is to avoid to build your own static site. You can get a similar service bundled with other advantages on Medium
Everything starts with the idea to build a website to host my work. On the road, it became obvious that the first article has to be precisely on how to do it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>